Name: Noha Nabil Erian

Mobile 002- 01222217431

Address: Third District – New Cairo Email: nohanabilerian@gmail.com

Dear Hiring Manager,

I'm a pharmacist with 20+ years of work experience, in teaching, marketing research, pharmaceutical sales and patients' education.

My work experience and related studies qualified me to master internet searches and preparing presentations in the medical and educational areas (in both English and French), exploring and creating ideas to deliver information and creating good connections

My extracurricular activities working on events planning and travel activities for groups, and voice over exercises in Arabic, English and French enriched my creativity, organization and communication skills.

What qualifies me for consideration:

- Vast experience for more than 8+ years in creating teaching content and aiding materials/medicalpresentations for students
- Good Pharmacovigilance Practice certification
- Experience in creating and facilitating groups travel activities and event coordination
- Touch typing skills
- Extracurricular activities experience includes, themed events planning and execution activities

Academic studies:

- Good Pharmacovigilance Practice (GVP) at Vigihub (2021)
- Online Family Counseling Course at Udacity 2001
- School principle Training Certificate 50 hours Udacity 2020
- Touch Typing and medical transcription Certificate at Allied Information Technology 2004
- Chemistry and biology teaching courses at the British Council (2008)
- Bachelor of pharmaceutical sciences, Faculty of Pharmacy, Helwan University. (2002)

Personal skills:

- Team player who quickly builds trust and collaborative working relationships.
- Excellent presentation skills, teaching students for 8+ years
- · Strong communication skills in Arabic, English and French
- Out of the box thinker known for figuring out creative new ways to do things better
- Passionate about and experienced in transferring knowledge to others.
- Strong **stakeholder management** experience, with the ability to build and strengthen relationships within the business at all levels.
- Confidence in handling conflicts.
- Thirst to taking new challenges

To further acquaint you with the specifics of my background, I am enclosing my resume – full details are enclosed.

Thank you in advance for your time and consideration. I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely, **Noha**

Mobile 002- 01222217431 Address: Third District – New CairoEmail:

nohanabilerian@gmail.com

Date of Birth: May 1980

Work Experience:

- * working as **a patient support specialist** at **curenta pharmacy** usa ,from february 2023 till may 2023, handling patients complains, achieving patient satisfaction.
 - Medical Translation and Transcription at Kantar Health, Ipsos and IMS (2010 2014 2020 till Currently)
 - > Translation of medical marketing research materials (questionnaires and discussion guides)
 - > Transcriptions of In-depth interviews with doctors
 - Science Teacher for grades 5 and 6 at MSE American System (2016 2020)
 - > Preparing science curriculum
 - Creating scientific related activities
 - Making exams content for the American Curriculum
 - Biology Teacher for grade 7 at British Ramsis School (2015 2016)
 - > Preparing science curriculum
 - Creating scientific related activities
 - > Preparing exams for the British Curriculum
 - Maternity Leave (2014)
 - English Instructor at Berlitz
 - Freelance transcriber and translator at Ipsos Egypt
 - Science Teacher for prep 3 at Noubarian Armenian School. (2012 2013)
 - Maternity Leave (2010 2012)
 - Freelance transcriber and translator at Kantar Health and IMS
 - Science Teacher, prep.3, primary 6 at New Horizon International School. (2009 2010)
 - Science Teacher, pre-IGCSE, grades 7 and 8 at Future's language School (2007 2008)
 - Science Teacher, prep 3, Egyptian Langue School (2006 2007)
 - Medical Representative, AT Global Napi Pharmaceuticals (Reumatoid Gyna –Ortho Lines) (2004 – 2005)
 - Events Coordination, patients' education then product specialist (GIT and Nutrition)at IMG (Dec 2003 – Dec 2004)
 - Community Pharmacist (Dec 2002 Dec 2003)

Education Background:

Good Pharmacovigilance Practice (GVP) at Vigihub - 2021

- Chemistry and biology teaching courses at the British council 2008 Bachelor of pharmaceutical sciences, Faculty of Pharmacy, Helwan University. (2002) High school" St. Joseph Language School, Heliopolis

References are Available Upon Request